{"data":[{"question":"When the girl caught sight of the ___, she gave a scream.","a":"field mice","b":"mice field","c":"mouses field","d":"field mouses","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Plural of \"mouse\" is mice \n- Field mouse: a type of mouse","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"He works form home every day, but he still gets good ___.","a":"pay","b":"wage","c":"income","d":"salary","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Pay: money that you are given for doing your job= most suitable for this case \n- Wage: money you earn that is paid according to the number of hours, days, or weeks that you work \n- Income:the money that you earn from your work or that you receive from investments, the government... \n- Salary: money that you receive as payment from the organization you work for, usually paid to you every month","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"The boss forgot both of the ___.","a":"room number","b":"rooms numbers","c":"room numbers","d":"room's numbers","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"That famous writer gives lessons in ___.","a":"the composition","b":"a composition","c":"compositions","d":"composition","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Give lessons in + subject = teach that subject","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"Biology is ___.","a":"science of the life","b":"science of life","c":"the science of life","d":"the science of the life","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Sciene: already be determined by \"biology\"- not use \"the\" \n- Life: general meaning= not use article","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"___ is more important than ___.","a":"A health, a wealth","b":"The health, the wealth","c":"Healths, wealths","d":"Health, wealth","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Health, wealth: uncountable noun \n- General speaking- not use article","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"What did you see? \"We saw ___ police there.\"","a":"much","b":"many","c":"the","d":"little","answer":"2","explain":"- Police is plural and countable noun-> much, little are not - This sistuation, police is not determined -> not + the","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"That bridge is only ___ long.","a":"five meter","b":"five-meters'","c":"five meters","d":"five-meters","answer":"3","explain":"- Structure: number + unit +long\/high: to express how long\/high one thing is","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"Mother made a new apron with two yards of ___.","a":"cloth","b":"clothes","c":"cloths","d":"dress","answer":"1","explain":"- Cloth: [uncountable] material used for making things such as clothes","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"Where is Bob? \"We just saw him in the ___.\"","a":"room of lunches","b":"lunch room","c":"room for lunches","d":"lunches room","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom) \n- Lunch room: room use for eating lunch \n- This case, \"room\" is singular ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"53","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"}]}